Hello, welcome to SubScreen. Start by pressing the Play button below (>).
Good! Playback has been initiated and this line will change to the next one shortly.
Next, try hitting the Next button to the bottom right. We'll wait.
Now hit the Play button below to resume playback.
These buttons can be used if you need
to manually resync the player for
some reason, such as commercials.
This program is capable of automatically
downloading subtitles from OpenSubtitles.org
Just hit the (Download) button, and type
the name of the movie or show.
Optionally, you can login to your OpenSubtitles account
or include only subtitles in a particular language.
Manually downloaded subtitle files should be placed in:
$SUBTITLE_FOLDER_PATH$
Finally, you can use the + or - buttons
to the left in order to adjust text size.
Thank you for downloading this app!
Press the Back button to return
to the file selection menu.